The Kingdom of Marinforest is home
to a human king and three fairy kings.
Thanks to the Forest Fairy King,
the land is blessed with abundance,
and its fertility is guaranteed.
Thanks to the Sky Fairy King,
the air is very clean,
and there is never a shortage
of life-giving rain.
Thanks to the Sea Fairy King,
things like coral, pearls,
and fish are abundant
and bring prosperity to the kingdom.
Everyone in the Marinforest
royal family is loved by the fairies
and has received their blessing.
The fairies' power is vital
in supporting the kingdom.
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
The Mermaid Knows Not of Love
I'll undergo bridal training
for the next year.
I do feel a bit sad about
leaving my homeland.
What's wrong, Tiara?
Is something on your mind?
Prince Aqua...
No, I'm very excited to go to Marinforest.
I'm sure I will miss
my homeland at times,
but you'll be with me, so I'll be happy.
Oh, honestly... You always
say such adorable things.
If there's ever anything troubling you,
tell me right away.
I will.
Of course, if you tell me
you want to go home,
I don't have the slightest shred
of confidence that I could let you.
Prince Aqua...
Oh! Is that the border?
Yes.
On Lapis Lazuli's side, you can see roses,
but on Marinforest's side,
the border is decorated differently.
Wow! It's incredible!
I'll surprise you even more. Look.
So this is the Kingdom of Marinforest!
This is the first time
I've ever seen the ocean!
No need to rush.
The ocean won't run away.
It's Aquasteed and Elliot!
Welcome home!
How cute!
We're back.
Have you all been well?
I want to be friends with them, too...
Let's go over there.
Y-Yes, let's.
Maybe they'll be our friends.
Good day to you.
Ew! I hate you!
Don't touch us!
Fairies are fickle creatures.
Y-Yes, I have heard people say so.
Who is this?
I know who!
They were calling her "Philine"!
I like Philine!
Why?! Lady Tiararose is
far more worthy of your favor!
Oh, don't worry about me.
I do feel sad that
they don't like me, though.
You can take your time, Tiara.
In fact, I'm actually relieved
they didn't take you from me.
Prince Aqua...
Huh?
Icilla Pearllant
Lady Icilla?
Huh?
The sequel's heroine is a duke's
daughter in Marinforest named Icilla,
and just when Prince Aqua
is feeling fed up with
the fiancée the state chose for him,
he meets her on the seashore!
Prince Aquasteed,
it's so good to see you again.
Yes, it has been a while.
Did you swim all the way here?
Yes, I was swimming with the
sea fairies, and I ended up here.
Welcome home, Prince Aquasteed.
And... this is someone
I haven't met before, yes?
My name is Icilla Pearllant.
This is my fiancée.
Oh!
My name is Tiararose Lapis Clamentile.
I'm very happy to meet you.
The Pearllants are the ducal family
that oversees the oceans.
Icilla is skilled at raising fish,
corals, and other things in the sea.
She always helps me with my work.
Oh, I see!
I'll do my best to continue
to be useful to you!
Oh, and please come visit
our house again soon.
I always looked forward to your visits.
Of course. I'll visit soon.
Is it possible that I'm the
villainess in the sequel as well?
Yes, my existence is definitely irregular.
I might be completely
removed from the story.
If I am, then once again...
Excuse me. I'm going to rest
by the carriage for a bit.
Huh?
I wasn't expecting the heroine
to show up so soon.
I don't want to lose Prince Aqua.
What should I do now?
What face should I make when I return?
I'm not confident that I can act cheerful.
How troubling.
You're troubled?
Forest... fairies?
What's your name?
Oh, my name is
Tiararose Lapis Clamentile.
Tiara! Nice to meet you!
I love Tiara!
I can't believe it.
Forest fairies
don't normally like people,
yet they're blessing her?
Elliot? What brings you here?
Oh, I apologize.
I've been following behind
at a short distance to guard you.
Did you wander out here alone
because something is wrong?
No, I'm all right.
I was in the carriage for a long time,
so I wanted to stretch my legs.
Tiara, you're not happy?
This flower is really tasty!
It's blessed by the forest fairies!
Eat it! Eat it!
It's delicious.
She feels better now!
Tiara!
I'm sorry. I was walking around
over there a bit.
Please don't worry me so much.
Take me with you next time.
I will.
Are you hungry?
I brought some sweets with me.
No, I'm all right.
I'm so fortunate.
Instead of being so afraid of the heroine,
I should treasure all the wonderful
people who support me.
The Castle of Marinforest
I bet you've never taken such
a long carriage ride before.
Are you feeling all right?
Yes.
As I mentioned, there'll be
a welcome party for you in three days.
I will arrange a dress for you,
of course, so please wear it.
You'll arrange a dress for me?
I'm so happy! Thank you!
Oh, darn it all...
You're so adorable.
P-Prince Aqua...
A whole year until we're married?
That's too long.
I want to make you my wife right now.
Prince Aqua, don't be like that.
I'm going to complete my bridal training
and be helpful to you as your wife.
Just wait a bit longer.
I know.
What do you think?
I gave you the half-up style that's
popular in Marinforest right now.
It's lovely. Thank you.
You've always been so good
at doing my hair.
This is where we encounter a problem.
What should we do about a hair accessory?
I'd like something that looks
special for the occasion.
In that case, how about these?
They were all picked
from the castle courtyard.
Flowers like these are
a specialty of Marinforest.
They're lovely! Aren't they, Philine?
Yes, I'm sure they'll suit you perfectly.
Um... do you have one
in a deep blue color?
A deep... blue?
I thought it might be nice to wear one
the same color as Prince Aqua's hair.
Oh! That's a very good idea!
I'm very sorry, but there are
no blue flowers this time of year.
Oh, I see...
What could this mean?!
It must be a gift from the forest fairies!
A gift?
Yes. You may be the only one
in the kingdom right now
who's received
the forest fairies' blessing.
There are some who are blessed
by the sea or sky fairies,
but we never hear of anyone being
blessed by the forest fairies.
Amazing! Isn't this wonderful,
Lady Tiararose?
Yes!
Honestly, my Tiara
is so adorable, it hurts.
Huh?
Those blue roses in your hair
are beautiful, as well.
They're the same color as my hair,
so it feels as if I'm under the illusion
that all of you belongs to me.
But all of me does belong
to you, Prince Aqua.
I am deeply honored to meet you.
I hope we will enjoy a favorable
relationship for years to come.
Lady Tiararose, Marinforest
warmly welcomes you.
King of Marinforest
Sotiris Marinforest
We are terribly pleased to have
a lovely young lady like you here.
Queen
Lavina Marinforest
You honor me, Your Majesty.
I will devote myself
to my studies for the next year
in hopes of supporting
Prince Aquasteed.
I'm so looking forward to
the future that lies ahead.
No matter what happens,
I won't run away this time.
Prince Aquasteed, Lady Tiararose,
congratulations on your engagement.
Thank you, Lady Icilla.
What do you think of Marinforest?
Are you able to live here
without difficulty?
Yes. Prince Aquasteed is taking
very good care of me, as well.
I'm so glad to hear that!
I would love to become
better friends with you.
Please pay a visit to my home sometime.
Huh?
Lady Icilla's mansion sits next
to the foremost ocean in Marinforest.
I'm sure you would love it.
Oh, I see.
I would love to visit sometime.
I'm so happy!
I'll show you
the finest hospitality I can!
All right. Thank you very much.
I don't want to get involved with her,
but she's moving in quick!
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
I'm actually going to
visit Lady Icilla now.
Are you all right?
Yes. I'm sorry to ask this of you, Tarmo.
Not at all. I am your personal
knight, Lady Tiararose.
You are free to ask anything of me.
Thank you.
Lady Tiararose,
thank you for coming to visit!
Thank you for inviting me, Lady Icilla.
Please, follow me.
I'll show you around the garden.
All right.
Oh, my! I've never seen
such pretty fish before!
The water in this fountain is seawater.
These little fish are a rare species
that only lives in my ocean.
She's definitely the sequel's heroine.
Her backstory is solid.
I've prepared tea for you.
Thank you.
The ocean is just
as beautiful as I've heard.
Would you like to try going in it?
What?
Oh, that's not what I mean!
I've been blessed by the sea fairies,
so I can use magic that makes
breathing underwater possible.
I can even make
a layer of air around your body
so you can go in the water
without getting your clothes wet.
You can do that?
She's definitely the sequel's heroine.
Anything goes.
Do I stand a chance
against a kind heroine
who's loved by the fairies?
My father told me
that you and Prince
Aquasteed met at school.
Yes.
So you two will be marrying out of love?
That's wonderful!
What does that mean?
Does Lady Icilla not love Prince Aqua?
You are beautiful yourself, Lady Icilla.
Aren't you surrounded by men
who won't leave you alone?
Lady Tiararose, please!
That isn't so at all!
I have entrusted every aspect
of my engagement to my father.
I'm happy as long as I can be in the sea.
See how beautifully the fish
and coral have grown?
But are there no men
you've fallen in love with?
No. It's embarrassing to admit,
but I've yet to fall in love.
It seems hard to believe
she could be lying.
How can someone be so pure,
sweet, and honest?
Would you like to go into the ocean now?
There are so many cute fish there!
Yes, I'd love to.
Grant us your blessing
to dive into the blue depths.
Incredible!
They don't even run away from humans?
No. I'm down here in the ocean every day,
so I'm friends with the fish.
She's like a sea goddess.
The coral is beautiful, too.
You make accessories
and things from it, right?
Yes, thankfully, there are
many who favor our coral products.
How wonderful!
I never dreamed I'd be
able to walk under the sea.
To think there was such a
beautiful world to be found down here.
I'm so glad you're enjoying it.
I'll go back up first
and prepare some warm tea.
Oh, I'll go with you.
No, please, take this opportunity
to enjoy yourself.
The fish are happy you're here, too!
All right, then, I will.
It seems like she really
is a good person.
And yet, here I was...
It's so pretty. I'm glad I came here.
Prince Aqua?
No... But why?
Is this the power of the game?
Did I get between
the two of them after all?
No! I decided I wouldn't run away!
This time, I have to make sure
I get my feelings across!
Tiara, I came to pick you up.
Please don't leave me alone, Prince Aqua!
Oh, it's no use. You're too cute, Tiara.
Oh, my!
This concludes our tour
of the castle interior.
If you like, I could also show you
the forest behind the castle.
Beautiful flowers bloom there.
Oh, I would love to see it!
Huh?
I'm sure they're
discussing work, as always.
But why on the terrace?
He said he'd be
in his office all day today.
See? It looks like they're both
returning to his office now.
So it does. I'm sorry.
It seems I was overthinking things.
Oh, my!
It really is beautiful!
Hey, it's Tiararose!
Hi, Tiara!
Hello. I see you're
as energetic as ever today.
By the way, I have
some cookies. Want some?
Yay! I do!
They're so crispy!
Yummy! I love them!
Th-They're so cute!
Tiara! Over here!
What is it?
The king is up ahead!
The king?
Huh?!
Over here!
Um... Fairy?
Where am I?
So you are Tiararose?
King!
The king... of the forest fairies?!
Tiara in the Sleeping Forest
The forest fairies love you,
and you make good cookies?
I approve.
You may stay in my forest
as long as you like.